Guide to the BOMB Magazine Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
BOMB Magazine Records,
1978-2005
153.81 linear feet (121 record storage cartons, 6 archival document boxes, and 3 flat boxes)
Columbia University. Rare Book and Manuscript Library, New York, NY. 10027
MS#1415
6256785
This collection contains the administrative records of the interview-based arts journal, BOMB Magazine
Historical Note
BOMB Magazine was founded in 1981 as a medium through which artists could speak to one another freely and without boundaries about the creative process; what it meant to them as writers, actors, directors, artists and cultural commentators. The editors, being unsure of the success of this venture, named the magazine BOMB. However, the concept of providing a forum for artists to discuss art, literature, film, and fashion in print was indeed successful and the magazine has continued for over twenty-five years.
Located in Brooklyn, New York, BOMB Magazine is published quarterly by the small non-profit New Art Publications. The magazine has an editorial board consisting of some seventy members who are actively involved in the creative and performing arts. This organization exists financially through grants, given at the local and national level, and donations. BOMB's Art Program provides further income for the institution. Through this program, artists donate artwork to the magazine which then sells these pieces to art collectors, museums, and university galleries. Some individuals who have been involved with this program in the past are Keith Haring, William Wegman, and several artists who created publicity pieces for the popular Absolut Vodka marketing campaign.
Throughout the years, many notable members of the arts have conducted or been interviewed for BOMB Magazine. In addition to the interviews, BOMB staff members have reviewed literary pieces, have reproduced artwork, and have included articles on theater productions and film. Indeed, the variety of artists who have graced the pages is broad. Selected distinguished individuals include Jane Alexander, Laurie Anderson, Eric Bogosian, Jean Louis Borges, Chuck D, Willem Dafoe, Jill Eisenstadt, Spaulding Gray, Christopher Guest, Emmylou Harris, bell hooks, Jim Jarmusch, Jasper Johns, Wong Kar-Wai, Roy Lichtenstein, Robert Mapplethorpe, Joyce Carol Oates, Salman Rushdie, Quentin Tarantino, and Wallace Shawn.
BOMB Magazine continues to provide an in-depth look at the ways in which art is appreciated, created and sustained by those most involved: the artists.
Scope and Content
The bulk of the collection is comprised of research and background material used by the BOMB staff to create the individual issues. These records include correspondence, interview transcripts, literary manuscripts and proofs, magazine layouts, photographs and slides of individual artists and artwork, research material, printed material, and audio and digital files. Administrative files, such as financial records, fundraising material, legal files, records concerning other BOMB publications and programs, and general business records are also held in the collection.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into three series
Series I: Administrative Records, 1981-2003
Subseries I.1: Art Collectors Program, 1981-2003
Subseries I.2: Development and Finances, 1985-2003
Subseries I.3: Website, 1984-2003
Series II: BOMB Publications, 1981-2005
Subseries II.1: Issues, 1981-2005
Subseries II.2: Monographs, 1991-1998
Series III: Research Material, 1978-2004
Subjects
Copley, Billy.; Girouard, Tina.; Haring, Keith, 1958-1990; Lopate, Phillip, 1943-; Martinez, Daniel J., 1957-; Sussler, Betsy.; Wegman, William, 1943-; Art--Interviews.; Arts, Modern--20th century--Periodicals.; Avant-garde (Aesthetics)--History--20th century--Periodicals.; Experimental drama, American.; Intercultural communication in the performing arts.; Performing arts--Interviews.; Performing arts and literature--New York (State)--Brooklyn (New York); Theater--Interviews.; Exhibition Catalogs; Layouts; Manuscripts for publication
Access Restrictions
The following boxes are located off-site: Boxes 1 through 119 and 125. You will need to request this material from the Rare Book and Manuscript Library at least twenty-four (24) hours in advance to use the collection in the Rare Book and Manuscript Library reading room.
This collection has no restrictions.
Related Material
BOMB Magazine has a website called BOMB Interactive which is available to users through its website. http://www.bombsite.com
Acquisition
BOMB Magazine. Purchase, October 2005
- Series I: Administrative Records, 1981-2003
  Series I holds the administrative records of Bomb Magazine. This series is arranged in three subseries: Art Program, Development and Finances, and Website.
  - Subseries I.1: Art Program, 1981-2003
    The Art Program records document the planning and execution of this financially based initiative. The files consist of artist's biographical material, correspondence, reviews, exhibition catalogues, artist catalogues, and press clippings. Visual material is well represented in the form of photographs and slides of the individual pieces of art. Some digital files may be found in this subseries containing scanned images of artwork and word documents concerning the artists and their work. Several original pieces of artwork are held in the collection by the artists Keith Haring, William Wegman, Billy Copley, and Tina Girouard.
    - General Administrative and Financial Records
      - Correspondence, undated (Box 18, 37, 52, 89)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks, undated, (3 1/2 inches) (Box 82)
      - Donation Records, undated (Box 18, 37, 52)
      - Donor Lists, undated (Box 18, 37, 52)
      - Financial Statements, undated (Box 18, 37, 52)
      - Press Releases, undated (Box 18, 37, 52)
      - Publicity Materials, undated (Box 18, 37, 52)
    - General Artist Records
      - Biographical Material, undated (Box 19, 37)
      - Contracts, undated (Box 19, 37)
      - Correspondence, undated (Box 19, 37)
      - Digital Files--CD-R, undated (Box 19)
      - Digital Files--Zip Disks, undated (Box 19, 37)
      - Printed Material--General, 1998 (Box 19, 37)
      - Printed Material--Artist's Catalogs, 1995-2003 (Box 63)
    - Art
      - Copley, Billy--"Absolut #1," 1999 (Box 13V-J-5)
      - Girouard, Tina--"Voodoo & Vodka" and "Louisiana Spirits," 1991 (Mapcase 13V-J-5)
      - Haring, Keith--"One Hundred Cocks for Verlane and Richard," 1985 June 11 (Mapcase 13V-J-5)
      - Les Enfants Terrible. Children of the Game by Philip Glass and Susan Marshall, undated (Mapcase 13V-J-5)
      - Speak Theater and Film!, undated (Mapcase 13V-J-5)
      - Martinez, Daniel J.--"Freedom Is," 1990 December 1 (Box 105)
    - Art--Photographs
      - General, undated (Box 45, 52)
      - Ando, Joe--Oils on Paper, 1995 (Box 19)
      - Bleckner, Ross, undated (Box 19)
      - Graupe-Pillard, Grace--"Manipulation/Massacre," undated (Box 37)
      - Morley, Malcolm--Images of Four Watercolors, 1985-1989 (Box 37)
    - Art--Slides
      - General, undated (Box 45)
      - Acconci Studio--"A City That Rides the Garbage Dump," 1999 (Box 19)
      - Artist Studio Benefit Tour, 2000 April 29 (Box 19)
      - Barney, Tina, undated (Box 19)
      - Bedia, Jose, undated--Chromogenic Prints, 1988-1990 (Box 19)
      - Bidlo--"Not Warhol (Brillo Box)," 1991 (Box 19)
      - Bloom, Barbara--"Untitled," 1988 (Box 19)
      - Casebere, James--"Four Flooded Archies from Right," 1999 (Box 19)
      - Chandler, Michael--Oil on Paper, 1994-1996 (Box 19)
      - Charlesworth, Sarah--"Text," 1994 (Box 37)
      - Charlesworth, Sarah--"Levitating Buddha," undated (Box 19)
      - Chu, Anne--"House with Bamboo Trees and Court Lady" (detail), 1999 (Box 19)
      - Copley, Billy, 1992-1995 (Box 19)
      - Coyne, Petah--"Untitled (#1018P-01)," 2001 (Box 19)
      - Crane, Gregory, 1991-1999 (Box 19)
      - Elliot, Jeremy, 2000 (Box 19)
      - Ess, Barbara--"Wildlife" Photograph, 1996 (Box 19)
      - Fischer, R.M., 1992-1994 (Box 19)
      - Fishman, Louise--"Double Dutch," 1994 (Box 19)
      - Fowler, Roy, 1994-1995 (Box 19)
      - Goldin, Nan--"Cookie at a Restaurant, Positano," 1986 (Box 19)
      - Greenbaum, Joanne--"Untitled," 2000 (Box 19)
      - Hamilton, Mary--Oil on Canvas, 1994-1995 (Box 19)
      - Haring, Keith--"One Hundred Cocks for Verlane and Richard," 1985 June 11 (Box 19)
      - Harper, Sharon--"Flug (Flight)," 2000 (Box 19)
      - Hatoum, Mona--"T42," 1993-1998 (Box 19)
      - Heighstein, 1998 (Box 19)
      - Heilmann, May--"Barstow," 1995 (Box 19)
      - Howland, R.--"Big Drawings," 1993 (Box 37)
      - Hudson, Judith, 1993, 2001 (Box 19)
      - Jaudon, Valerie--"Slightly Dangerous," undated (Box 19)
      - Jimenez, Ivelisse--Painting, undated (Box 19)
      - Kalina, Richard--"Attorney,"1999 (Box 19)
      - Kapp, David--"Early Morning Sidewalk," 2000 (Box 19)
      - Lemieux, Annette--"Motherland," 1993 (Box 52)
      - Leonard, Zoe--"Horse," 1994 (Box 19)
      - Lethbridge--"Untitled," 2001 (Box 19)
      - McClelland, Suzanne--"A Kind and Encouraging Word," 2000 (Box 19)
      - Means, Amanda--"Flower (Number 26)," 1996 (Box 19)
      - Milhazes, Beatriz--"Ovale," 2002 (Box 19)
      - Muniz, Vik--"The raft of medusa (from pictures of chocolate)," 1999 (Box 19)
      - Neshat, Shirin--"Untitled (Rapture Series-Women Pushing Boat)," 1999 (Box 19)
      - Newman, Laura--"Untitled," 2001 (Box 19)
      - Owens, Bill--Painting, undated (Box 19)
      - Pozzi, Lucio--"Knot Gone," 1998 (Box 19)
      - Schwartz, E.--"Untitled," 1981 (Box 19)
      - Seator, Glen, undated (Box 19)
      - Shapiro, Joel--"Untitled," 1995 (Box 19)
      - Siena, James--"Detroit," 1998 (Box 19)
      - Siverthorne, Jean, undated (Box 19)
      - Steir, Pat--"A Walk in the Woods," 2000 (Box 19)
      - Stuart, Michelle--"Brookings LXXXIII," undated (Box 19)
      - Sugiura, Kunie--"Stacks. Tulips. A4. positive 2/2," 1995 (Box 37)
      - Tomaselli, Fred--Collages, 1999-2000 (Box 19)
      - Uglow, Alan, undated (Box 19)
      - Westfall, Stephen--"S-13," 1995 (Box 19)
      - Zittel, Andrea--"Study for A-Z Perfected Pillow," undated (Box 19)
      - Unidentified, undated (Box 19, 45)
    - Miscellaneous Art Correspondence Archive
      - Jill Moser (Box 152)
      - Elizabeth Payne (Box 152)
      - Adelle Lutz (Box 152)
      - A Conversation Between Krystyna Borkowska and Alan Scarritt (Box 152)
      - Benefit Slides 2003 (Box 152)
      - Archive (Box 152)
      - Miscellaneous Archive (Box 152)
      - Slides (Box 152)
      - Cassette with Illegible Label (Box 152)
      - Correspondence of Betsy Sussler (Box 152)
  - Subseries II.2: Development and Finances, 1985-2003
    Subseries Two is comprised of records concerning the fiscal operations of BOMB Magazine. Included are budgets and ledgers, correspondence with board members and donors, donor lists, general mailing lists, financial statements, contracts in regards to other BOMB publications, subscription and distribution information. There are also records for grant applications, most notably the National Endowment for the Arts, and the New York State Council on the Arts (NYSCA).
    - General, undated
      - Advertising Contracts, 1985-1995 (Box 18, 74)
      - Audit, 1994 December 31 (Box 18)
      - Bank Statements, 1983-1984 (Box 94)
      - Board Members, 2001-2003 (Box 43)
      - Contracts, undated (Box 74)
      - Correspondence, undated (Box 16, 43, 69, 74)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks, undated (3 ½ inches) (Box 71)
      - Republic National Bank Loan Payment File, undated (Box 18)
    - Grants
      - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA), 1990-1996 (Box 30)
      - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA)--Digital Files--Floppy Disks, 1996-1999 (3 ½ inches) (Box 68)
      - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH), 2002 May 1-2004 May 1 (Box 18)
      - New York State Council on the Arts (NYSCA)--Application Materials, 1990-1996 (Box 30)
      - New York State Council on the Arts (NYSCA)--Application Materials, 1996-1997 (Box 57)
      - New York Foundation for the Arts (NYFA), 1998 (Box 18)
    - Ledger, undated (Box 9)
    - Sitting Pretty Benefit, 1998-1999, 2001-2003 (Box 18)
    - Sitting Pretty Benefit, 1999-2000 (Box 57)
    - Subscriptions
      - Agreements, 2000-2002 (Box 20)
      - Billing Statements, 2000-2002 (Box 20)
      - Correspondence, 1985-1995 (Box 74)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks, undated (3 ½ inches) (Box 68)
      - Distributors, 2000-2002 (Box 20)
        - Anderson News Company (Box 20)
        - Armadillo (Box 20)
        - Deboer (Box 20)
        - Desert Moon (Box 20)
        - Doormouse (Box 20)
        - Eastern News (Box 20)
        - International Periodical Distributors (Box 20)
        - Media Solutions (Box 20)
        - Newsways (Box 20)
        - Don Olson (Box 20)
        - One Source (Box 20)
        - Small Changes (Box 20)
        - Christ Stadler (Box 20)
        - Total Circulation Services (Box 20)
        - Ubiquity (Box 20)
        - Worldwide Media Service (Box 20)
        - Ingram (Box 20)
      - Geographical Distribution Charts, 2000-2002 (Box 20)
      - Indie Bookstores, 2000-2002 (Box 20)
  - Subseries 3: Website, 1984-2003
    This subseries documents the growth of the BOMB Website and the creation of the Online Archive and "BOMBLive!," a web-based interview series that was established in 2001. The bulk of the records are audio cassettes of online audio material used for "BOMBLive!" as well as cassettes of other published and unpublished interviews that are not associated with a particular issue. Printed matter consists of correspondence, legal records, such as contracts and release forms, exhibition and artist catalogues, and original manuscripts and magazine galleys created by author Phillip Lopate. Photographs, slides and negatives, or profiled artists and artwork are also found in this subseries.
    - General, 2001-2002 (Box 31)
      - Contracts (Box 31)
      - Correspondence--General (Box 31)
      - Correspondence-MP3Lit.com (Box 43)
      - Galleys (Box 31)
      - Image Captions (Box 31)
      - Material Release Forms (Box 31)
      - Online Documentation (Box 31)
      - Preservation Information (Box 31)
    - Audio Archives, 1984-2003 (Box 114)
    - BOMBLive!
      - Audio Files, 1993- (Box 114)
      - Digital Files--CD-R, 2002 December 12 (Box 55)
      - Phillip Lopate Documents, 1998 (Box 74)
- Series II: BOMB Publications, 1981-2005
  Series II: BOMB Publications comprise the bulk of the collection and holds records pertaining to the monthly magazine issues as well as the BOMB books entitled, Speak Art!, Speak Fiction and Poetry!, and Speak Theater and Film!, " which are compilations of interviews originally published in the magazine.
  - Subseries II.1: Issues, 1981-2005
    This subseries consists of the finished publication and any accompanying documentation used in the creation of the issue. Included with the general records are correspondence between the editors, in particular Editor-in-Chief Betsy Sussler, and the artists being featured in an issue, transcripts of interviews, literary texts, layouts and galleys, artist catalogues, exhibition material, and other bound materials concerning art and artists. Separated work that is also found in this subseries may consist of a copy of the individual issue, photographs, printed material, copies of literary texts, in the form of reader copies or proofs that have been identified as being incorporated into a particular issue. Audio and Digital files, such as Zip disks, floppy disks, audio cassette tapes, and VHS tapes containing interviews, scanned digital images of artists and artwork, potential galleys and layouts, and advertisements are held in this subseries as well. This subseries has been organized chronologically by issue number.
    - Issue 1, 1981 Spring
      - General (Box 78)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Issue (Box 100, 115)
      - Manuscripts and Proofs (Box 78)
      - Portrait Photographs (Box 78)
      - Stills (Box 78)
      - Table of Contents (Box 105)
    - Issue 2, 1981
      - General (Box 78)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Issue (Box 100, 115)
      - Manuscripts and Proofs (Box 78)
      - Photographs (Box 78)
      - Table of Contents (Box 105)
    - Issue 3, 1982
      - General (Box 78)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Issue (Box 100, 115)
      - Photographs (Box 78)
      - Table of Contents (Box 105)
    - Issue 4, 1982
      - General (Box 78)
      - Issue (Box 100, 115)
      - Photographs (Box 78)
      - Table of Contents (Box 105)
    - Issue 5, 1983
      - General (Box 79)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 79)
      - Issue (Box 100, 115)
      - Portrait Photographs (Box 79)
      - Table of Contents (Box 105)
    - Issue 6, 1983 Spring/Summer
      - General (Box 27)
      - Issue--Sculpture and Fiction (Box 27, 115)
      - Portrait Photographs (Box 27)
      - Table of Contents (Box 105)
    - Issue 7, 1985 Fall
      - General (Box 27)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Issue (Box 115)
      - Photographs (Box 27)
      - Table of Contents (Box 105)
    - Issue 8, 1983-1984 Winter
      - General (Box 27)
      - Artwork for Issue (Box 27)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Issue (Box 115)
      - Manuscripts and Proofs--Untitled by Elovich, Richard (Box 27)
      - Photographs (Box 27)
      - Table of Contents (Box 105)
    - Issue 9, 1984 Spring/Summer
      - General (Box 27)
      - Art--Photographs--Mexican Art (Box 27)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Issue (Box 102, 115)
      - Table of Contents (Box 105)
    - Issue 10, 1984 Fall
      - General (Box 10)
      - Art--Photographs (Box 10)
      - Art--Slides (Box 10)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Issue (Box 10, 115)
      - Manuscripts and Proofs (Box 10, 115)
      - Table of Contents (Box 105)
    - Issue 11, 1984 Winter
      - General (Box 10)
      - Art--Photographs (Box 10)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Issue (Box 10, 115)
      - Manuscripts and Proofs (Box 10, 115)
      - Table of Contents (Box 105)
    - Issue 12, 1985 Spring/Summer
      - General (Box 10)
      - Art--Photographs (Box 10)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Issue (Box 10, 115)
      - Photographs (Box 10, 115)
      - Table of Contents (Box 105)
    - Issue 13, 1985 Fall
      - General (Box 73)
      - Art--Photographs (Box 73)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Issue (Box 115)
      - Publicity Photographs (Box 73)
      - Table of Contents (Box 105)
    - Issue 14, 1985-1986 Winter
      - General (Box 95)
      - Art--Photographs (Box 95)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Issue (Box 115)
      - Table of Contents (Box 105)
      - Manuscripts and Proofs (Box 95)
    - Issue 15, 1986
      - General (Box 73)
      - Art--Photographs (Box 73)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Issue (Box 73, 115)
      - Publicity Photographs (Box 73, 115)
      - Table of Contents (Box 105)
    - Issue 16, 1986 Summer
      - General (Box 95)
      - Art--Photographs (Box 95)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 68)
      - Issue (Box 115)
      - Manuscripts and Proofs (Box 95)
      - Table of Contents (Box 105)
    - Issue 17, 1986 Fall
      - General (Box 65)
      - Art--Photographs (Box 65)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Issue (Box 115)
      - Portrait Photographs (Box 65)
      - Table of Contents (Box 105)
    - Issue 18, 1987 Winter
      - General (Box 65)
      - Art--Photographs (Box 65)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Issue (Box 115)
      - Portrait Photographs (Box 65)
      - Table of Contents (Box 105)
    - Issue 19, 1987 Spring
      - General (Box 65)
      - Art--Photographs (Box 65)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Issue (Box 115)
      - Table of Contents (Box 105)
    - Issue 20, 1987 Summer
      - General (Box 65)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 68)
      - Issue (Box 115)
      - Photographs (Box 65)
      - Table of Contents (Box 105)
    - Issue 21, 1987 Fall
      - General (Box 105)
      - Art--Photographs (Box 105)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 68)
      - Issue (Box 116)
      - Manuscripts and Proofs (Box 105)
      - Table of Contents (Box 105)
    - Issue 22, 1988 Winter
      - General (Box 105)
      - Art--Photographs (Box 105)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 68)
      - Issue (Box 116)
      - Manuscripts and Proofs (Box 105)
      - Table of Contents (Box 105)
    - Issue 23, 1988 Spring
      - General (Box 102)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Issue (Box 116)
      - Publicity Photographs (Box 102)
      - Table of Contents (Box 105)
    - Issue 24, 1988 Summer
      - General (Box 102)
      - Art--Photographs (Box 102)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Issue (Box 116)
      - Table of Contents (Box 105)
    - Issue 25, 1988 Fall
      - General (Box 107)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Issue (Box 116)
    - Issue 26, 1988-1989 Winter
      - General (Box 105)
      - Art--Photographs (Box 105)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 105)
      - Issue (Box 116)
      - Manuscripts and Proofs (Box 105)
    - Issue 27, 1989 Spring
      - General (Box 107)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Issue (Box 116)
    - Issue 28, 1989 Summer
      - General (Box 107)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Issue (Box 116)
    - Issue 29, 1989 Fall
      - General (Box 87)
      - Art--Photographs (Box 87)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches, 5 ¼ inches) (Box 68, 87)
      - Issue (Box 116)
    - Issue 30, 1990 Winter
      - General (Box 87)
      - Art--Photographs (Box 87)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches, 5 ¼ inches) (Box 68, 87)
      - Issue (Box 116)
    - Issue 31, 1990 Spring
      - General (Box 46)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 68)
      - Issue (Box 116)
    - Issue 32, 1990 Summer
      - General (Box 46)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 68)
      - Issue 33, 1990 Fall (Box 116)
      - General (Box 97)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches) (Box 68, 71)
      - Issue (Box 116)
      - Portrait Photographs (Box 97)
        - Aborigine (Box 97)
        - Freud, Bella (Box 97)
        - Phillips, Dorothea (Box 97)
    - Issue 34, 1990-1991 Winter
      - General (Box 98)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches, 5 ¼ inches) (Box 68, 98)
      - Issue (Box 116)
      - Publicity Photographs--Metropolitan (Box 98)
    - Issue 35, 1991 Spring
      - General (Box 99)
      - Art--Photographs (Box 99)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 110)
      - Digital Files--Floppy Disks (3 ½ inches, 5 ¼ inches) (Box 68, 99)
      - Issue (Box 116)
    - Issue 36, 1991 Summer
      - General (Box 28)
      - Audio Files--Audio Cassettes (Box 111)